

Licensed cosmetologist equipped with over a decade of experience, an expertise in color, and a sharp grasp on social media's role in salon marketing. Experienced leader and manager with a history of sales growth a nd complaint resolution.

Professional Experience

Stylist/Assistant Manager

Allure Salon and Spa | August 2016 - Present

- Supervise 12 other stylists and give feedback on cuts, styling, color treatments, and customer service.
- Resolve customer complaints with a 70% success rate via phone, in-person, and using social media channels, such as Facebook and Yelp.
- Track employee hours and submit payroll.
- Educate clients on spa and hair productsand grew sales by 10% in the first three month.
- Complete inventory using Zenoti software.

Colorist

Toni & Guy, Los Angeles, CA | April 2013 - July 2016

- Provided state-of-the-art coloring services for all clients with all different hair types.
- Created a welcoming environment and encouraged individual requests.
- Attended frequent training regarding trends and innovations in color treatment.
- Served as lead colorist for six months while an individual was out on medical leave
- Held personal consults regarding color correction.

Hair Stylist

Hollywood Hair Studio, Beverly Hills, CA | June 2010 - April 2013

- Provided a complete range of hair care services for women and men and balanced 2-5 clients per hour.
- Greeted client's, signed them in, and booked appointments via phone calls.
- Sanitized equipment and workstations in accordance with local and state health code.
- Performed facials and unsold aftercare products.

123 Your Street, Los Angeles, CA 12345 madel inesmith @™ mple.co m (1231-456-7890

Education

IM Education Cosmetology Aveda Arts & Science Institute, Los Angeles, CA Septem be r 2010 - Octo ber 2011

MUD Makeup Certification Aveda Institute, Los Angeles, CA March 2017

Key Skills

- Time Management
- Customer Service
- Social Media
- · Styling Services
- · Beauty Consultations
- Salesmanship